An unromantic comedy.
Splitsville is a comedy film directed by Michael Angelo Covino.
After Ashley asks for a divorce, good-natured Carey runs to
his friends, Julie and Paul, for support.
He’s shocked to discover that the secret to their happiness is an open marriage, that is
until Carey crosses the line and throws all of their relationships into chaos.
Julie, played by Dakota Johnson.
Ashley, played by Adria Arjona.
Carey, played by Kyle Marvin.
Paul, played by Michael Angelo Covino.
Matt, played by Nicholas Braun.
Fede, played by David Castañeda.
Splitsville is a 2025 American comedy film directed by Michael
Angelo Covino, and written by Covino and Kyle Marvin.
It stars Dakota Johnson, Adria Arjona, Covino, and Marvin, and  follows two couples whose friendship erupts into
conflict when the husband of a divorcing couple sleeps with the wife of an open marriage couple.
Splitsville premiered at the Cannes Film Festival on May 19, 2025, and was released in select
theaters in the United States on August 22 by Neon before expanding wide on September 5.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of fish, pottery, fraud,
birthday party, open relationship.
The tone is lighthearted.